cracked.com 2007-05-14

# CRACKED.com - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Cracked Entertainment, Inc. (“ _Cracked_ ”) is committed to providing quality content, activities and information in print and online.  We take your right to privacy very seriously and strive to protect the online safety and privacy of all visitors to this Website (as defined in our “ _Terms and Conditions_ ”).

Because of its importance, and to make it easier for you to find and review it, we have made this privacy policy statement (the “ _Privacy Policy_ ”) into a separate document on the Website. 

Please take time to read the entire Privacy Policy carefully.  However, please bear in mind that the Privacy Policy is only one part of our agreement with you and that our Terms and Conditions (and other agreements) may also apply. We again remind you to check back here and to our Terms and Conditions often to be sure you remain mindful of all terms and conditions that apply to you when you use the Website.

**Introduction**

Cracked has established and set forth this Privacy Policy in order to inform you of our policies and practices regarding how we collect personal identifiable information from you, how we use and disclose it and your rights with respect to such information. By using this Website, you acknowledge and agree to all of the terms and conditions of Cracked’s Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, then please do not use this Website. In addition to this Privacy Policy, please take time to read the Website’s Terms and Conditions before using or accessing this Website.

**Disclosure (General)** : 

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your information.  While no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure from intrusion, we have used and will continue to use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the protection of your information. We continually assess new technology for protecting information and, when appropriate, we upgrade our information security systems. 

Although your privacy is very important to us, in this legal and technical environment, we cannot fully ensure that your personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties. Please see the "Disclosure to Third Parties" section below for more information.

The Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Cracked does not own or control, or to people that Cracked does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Cracked affiliates have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on their respective links.  You may also find additional information regarding privacy and safe web searching on the FTC’s website at <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.htm>

We reserve the right to change or modify our Privacy Policy from time to time simply by posting a revised version on this Website. Any such change shall be effective immediately upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. Furthermore, we reserve the right to make the revised or changed Privacy Policy effective for information we already have about you, as well as any information we receive in the future. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy practices.

**Privacy Policy**

Like many websites, we gather information about how visitors use this Website. In general, you can visit many of the web pages on this Website without telling us who you are or revealing personal information about yourself. 

When we use the term “personally identifiable information,” we mean information such as your full name, street address, town or city, state, zip code, country, telephone number, username, instant-messenger nickname, date of birth, e-mail address and any other information which we may collect from you that would allow someone to identify you or contact you. Personally identifiable information also includes information about your transactions, interaction or relationship with us if you have been a customer or user. 

For example, if you use or order any of our products or services, in addition to your name and contact information, we may also collect and maintain your billing address, shipping address, product selections, your credit card or other payment instrument information, your order number and information about your computer’s Internet address and/or website which may have referred or directed you to us and our Website (for example, the referring URL). 

We collect this and other information to fill your order, to communicate with you about your order and to send you promotional materials. 

We may also track the numbers of visitors to the Website.  We use such tracking information on an aggregated basis to help us operate the Website, enhance and improve the user experience, improve the look of our Website and to display advertising and marketing information. 

We collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Website and input information, whether you are registering to use the Website, enrolling or signing up for features and functions, participating in promotions and activities, ordering or purchasing products or services or in the course of any other exchanges of information, transactions and activities. We may use the information we obtain from you, including personally identifiable information, to tailor your experience on the Website, to display content we think may be of interest to you, or to let us customize what you see when you visit the Website according to your preferences. Some features and functions of the Website require you to register or obtain our permission before you can use them - for security, identification and marketing reasons, among others - and as part of that process we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. In addition, during the registration process we will also ask you to select (or we may provide) a user ID and password (we will allow you to change your password, as well as any personally identifiable information you may have given us in order to keep this information current). Among other things, this information helps us securely identify you as a registered or permitted user of those features and functions. Bear in mind that when you submit information to us, it does not guarantee that we will permit you to use any or all of the features or functions of the Website.

The personally identifiable information you provide to us, as well as any information, personal or otherwise, that you create and which may be saved on or in association with the Website, is used to provide you with better service. It allows us to save you time and better understand your needs. It also helps us help you learn more about your preferences and those goods and services that may be of interest to you. For example, we track your information to assist us in confirming and filling orders, producing reports, maintaining quality control, administering and managing the Website and our business, and, whenever it may become necessary or appropriate, to contact you concerning your orders, your transactions or any other activities associated with the Website. We may use your personally identifiable information to advise you of goods or services, which may be available from us, our sponsors and advertisers. If you are a registered user, you also acknowledge, understand and hereby agree that you are giving us your consent to track your activities and your use of the Website and its functions and features, in connection with your registration and use of the Website.

We may also track your Internet Protocol (IP) address and other anonymous information from your web browser for trends and statistics (including, but not limited to, browser version, pages requested and pages visited), but you will remain anonymous unless you provide us with personal information during your visit to this Website or during an earlier or subsequent visit and we are able to link your IP address between your current visit and one of these other visits. 

We also work with service providers who use tracking technologies to serve ads across the Internet or track email communication response rates on our behalf. These companies may collect personal information about your visits to this Website and your interaction with our communications, including advertising.

In addition to anonymous information, we also collect personal information from you at this Website when you voluntarily submit it to us. We request personal information from you (which may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, gender, year of birth, and when necessary, credit card information) when you: (a) complete a registration, survey, application or other form; (b) purchase a product or service from us or from one of our vendors, suppliers or other agents; (c) sign-up to receive email newsletters or other correspondence; (d) participate in a promotion, contest, sweepstakes or similar promotional activity; (e) submit materials to our Website; (f) request a catalog or other materials from us; and/or (g) request e-mail, fax, mail, or telephone support or services.

We also collect information about your activities on and through this Website from our third party business partners, suppliers, vendors and other agents. You may choose not to provide us with any personal information. In such event, you can still access and use many portions of this Website; however, you will not be able to access and use those portions of this Website or the services available on or through this Website that require your personal information.

**Using Information**

We may use the information we collect to: (a) customize and/or personalize your communications, surfing, viewing and/or shopping experience; (b) better respond to your customer service inquiries; (c) communicate with you about your purchase, account information or customer service needs; (d) communicate with you about our products and events and for other promotional purposes; (e) improve our business; (f) administer contests, promotions, surveys or other website features; (g) provide technical support to you; and (h) perform any other lawful acts except for those acts expressly prohibited by the terms and conditions set forth herein.

**Sharing Information**

Except as expressly set forth herein, we do not loan, give away, sell, distribute or rent your personal information to any third party.

We will disclose your personal information to third parties if you have previously consented to such disclosures and in special circumstances, including, but not limited to, the sale of Cracked; the due diligence in connection with a potential sale of Cracked; any bankruptcy, insolvency or liquidation of Cracked or in other similar circumstances.

For the purpose of operating our business and providing you with certain services and products and to process your purchases, shipments and payments, we may disclose your personal information to one or more of our business partners, distributors, suppliers, affiliates, service providers or other third parties who are assisting Cracked in performing such services. Without limiting the foregoing, these third parties may provide Cracked with credit card processing, shipping, data management, email distribution, live text chat, email response, market research, information analysis and promotions management services. We provide such parties with the personal information they need to perform their respective services and we use commercially reasonable efforts to require them to safeguard your personal information and limit their use of it.

We also may provide your personal information to companies affiliated with Cracked (including, but not limited to, affiliates, subsidiaries and our parent companies) who may use your personal information for any legal purposes whatsoever.

We also may disclose personal information about you upon request by the government; in response to a court order; when required by law or when we believe in good faith is required by law; to enforce our Privacy Policy, terms and conditions or other agreements on this Website; upon your request; or to contact, identify or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with our or others’ rights or property. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing purposes.

We may also provide aggregated, non-personally identifiable information to third parties for any legal purposes whatsoever.

**Protecting Your Information**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard and secure your personal information while stored on our computer systems. We use a variety of industry standard security measures, including encryption and authentication tools, to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information. Your personal information is stored behind industry standard firewalls and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who are authorized to access such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. Regardless of these efforts by us, no system connected to the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

We use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard and secure the transmission of your personal information from your computer to our computers. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. To the extent you select the secure server method and your browser supports such functionality, all credit card information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Regardless of these efforts by us, no data transmission over the public Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

To help protect your computer and personal information, make sure you have current anti-virus and firewall software installed on your computer and update such software on a regular basis. Also, please review your credit card statement carefully and verify that all transactions are authorized and report any discrepancies immediately to your credit card company.

**Cookies**

This Website uses cookies. A cookie is a small, removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies allow you to place an order on this Website and allow us to enhance, facilitate and personalize your online surfing and shopping experience. For example, we use cookies to: (a) remember the items in your shopping cart; (b) recognize you when you return to this Website; (c) enable you to use one-click checkout; (d) present relevant content to you when you visit this Website; (e) analyze visitor behavior; and (f) facilitate other similar type of activities.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser settings. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your visit to this Website more efficient and enjoyable, and in some cases, some of our services will not function or will function with limited capability. However, with respect to our store, you can still place orders over contacting our customer service center at [Orders@CrackedStore.com](mailto:Orders@CrackedStore.com)

**Children's Online Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18. This Website is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under the age of 18 and we have made commercially reasonable efforts to design this Website to prevent our knowing acceptance of any such information.

It is possible that by fraud, deception or error, we may receive information pertaining to children under the age of 18. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of personal information belonging to a child under the age of 18, please do so at [webeditor@cracked.com](mailto:webeditor@cracked.com)

**Email Marketing Practices**

We adhere to the highest standards in our email marketing practices. When you choose to opt-into our email communications and submit your email address to us, we will send you an email requesting your confirmation. If you do not click on the confirmation link in the email, you will not be registered to receive our emails. This protects your inbox from unwanted emails should someone else provide your email address, or should you change your mind.

**Chat Rooms and Forums**

This Website may now or in the future include web logs ( _i.e._ , blogs), chat rooms, post-it boards, forums, message boards and/or news groups. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution before disclosing your personal information via these public venues, which you do at your own risk. If you do so, you may receive, among other things, unsolicited emails or “spam” from others. Cracked cannot safeguard the privacy of personal information that is disclosed online in this manner.

**Other Websites**

When browsing this Website, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control. These other websites may use cookies and pixel tags, collect data, or solicit personal information. Even though Cracked may be affiliated with these websites, we have no control over them or how they collect, distribute or otherwise use your personal information or how they safeguard and secure your personal information. Cracked is not responsible or liable for the conduct, policies or actions of the owners of such websites or the content displayed on these websites. These websites are linked to this Website only for your convenience and you access them at your own risk.

**Unsubscribing, Removing or Modifying Your Information**

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. To modify or delete any or all of the personal information you have provided to us, please login and update your profile. You may unsubscribe from receiving emails, and other correspondence from us including, but not limited to, faxes and U.S. postal service mail, at any time by using the link, or by contacting us using the information, included at the bottom of each email communication. You may also unsubscribe by sending us an email at [webeditor@cracked.com](mailto:webeditor@cracked.com)

In some limited circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions, we may retain in our files information you have requested to remove. Further, your personal information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical constraints and the fact that we back up our systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications related to this Website that are considered part of your account, such as technical alerts, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

**Terms and Conditions**

Cracked has a Terms and Conditions Agreement that sets forth the terms and conditions under which we provide products, services and information to you from this Website, and your use of, and access to, this Website. It is your responsibility to read, understand and comply with the terms and conditions set forth therein.

**Questions and Feedback**

This Website is operated by Cracked Entertainment, Inc. Our office address is:

Cracked Entertainment, Inc.   
35 West 35th Street  
6th Floor  
New York, New York 10001 USA

We may also be reached via email at [webeditor@cracked.com](mailto:webeditor@cracked.com) or you may call us at 212-444-7777. We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices. Please send us feedback pertaining to these matters or any other issue you may have with Cracked or this Website. If you feel that we are not following our stated Privacy Policy, you may also contact state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, your state or local consumer protection office, or The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202-FTC-HELP (202-382-4357) or at [http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm](file:///tp/%2F%2Fwww.ftc.gov%2Fftc%2Fcomplaint.htm)

As of January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding the disclosure of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please send an email to [webeditor@cracked.com](mailto:webeditor@cracked.com) or write to us at:

Cracked Entertainment, Inc.  
35 West 35th Street  
6th Floor  
New York, New York 10001 USA
